Viewers all over the world, join us in prayer.
You are here and we are there.
Anywhere you are, right now, begin to come against every pain, every affliction,
in your blood, in your veins, in your muscles, in your bones, in your tubes, in your stomach,
anywhere in your system, I say, "Out!"
You sickness, out! You affliction, out!
Out in your blood, bones, muscles, liver, tubes.
Right now, in the name of Jesus, I command them out!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua. Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name.
Viewers all over the world, you are here, we are there.
The presence of God is all over you.
The affliction in your bones, in your kidneys, in your liver, in your organs,
you must go, in the name of Jesus!
I say, "Go!" in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua. Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name.
I say, you, go! Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Viewers all over the world, your finances, business, career. I mean, your destiny, I mean your vision, have been released!
Have been rescued, in the name of Jesus!
Say, "It has been rescued!"
My finances, business, career, vision, destiny, have been rescued!
Thank you, Jesus! In Jesus' name!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua. Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here, to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and to stay up-to-date with our latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons, and testimonies,
from The Synagogue Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV. Changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.